[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[grunting]
[Kihyun] When they hit you, you take it.
When they tell you to kneel, you kneel.
The weak get crushed by the strong.
That's just how the world works.
15 YEARS EARLIER, BUSAN
Come here! [grunts]
Why'd you bring this thing?
What? Were you gonna
put a bullet in my head? Huh?
[grunts]
A goddamn Jap like you
should know your place.
[panting] Your brother's probably off
to report his missing pistol,
but you're the one who stole it!
[both grunting]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
You see what happens, you bastard?
Know your damn place, kid. All right?
[spits]
[pants]
I'm taking this, by the way.
What a little shit.
-[yells]
-[grunts]
Get the hell off me!
[both grunting]
[both yell]
[gunshot]
[Kihyun] My brother always said,
"If you don't want to get crushed
by your enemies, crush them first."
Where is he?
[breathing heavily]
Give me the gun.
Go home and wait till later.
[♪ tense music playing]
[door opens]
[sighs]
[Kihyun] Kitae never asked me
why I killed the guy,
and I never asked
what he did with the body.
An unspoken agreement.
And that day,
the day I thought it was all over,
everything began.
[gunshot echoes]
[♪ theme music playing]
[phone rings]
This is Baek Kihyun.
Is Jang back?
Yes. May I help you with something?
He just got his hands
on the slush fund ledger.
Stay sharp, find out exactly
what's going on, and report back to me.
720-1879.
If anything happens, you call me.
Understood?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[exhales deeply]
[Geonyoung] If you want
your sister to live
and your niece to have a normal childhood,
you have to ensure you survive first.
[door opens]
-Sir.
-Yeah.
We're ready to move out.
If we arrest Cheon Seokjung,
will you question him yourself
or will somebody else do it?
Baek Kihyun will be up to it.
Baek Kihyun's pretty green.
Let's give him a chance.
Did you request a warrant for Cheon?
Just tell me, and be honest.
Yes.
-You upset about that?
-What'd you charge him with?
I told you, we're taking him down
for his slush fund!
And what about the whole drug ring?
We're shifting the investigation
to go after the slush fund,
-not the drugs, Miss Oh.
-[Yejin] Sir, come on.
Are you sure you want this case
to get political?
-[Jaeho] Ugh, this girl.
-[shouts] "This girl"?
-Don't you dare talk to me like that!
-Colonel Ahn!
Just relax, both of you.
Ahn, get moving. Let's go.
Sir, we're moving out.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[door opens]
[Jaeho] When we arrest Cheon Seokjung…
[Yejin sighs]
If you let those politicians in uniform
pull your strings,
they'll stab you in the damn back.
SPECIAL ADVISOR JANG GEONYOUNG
[door closes]
[phone rings]
Yes?
This is Baek Kihyun. Where's my brother?
He's with Chief Cheon.
All right, Cheon is going to be arrested.
Orders came down.
You really think you can handle that?
Oh, it would be my pleasure.
I'll do it, my own way.
[♪ music continues]
[exhales]
-[knocks on door]
-[door opens]
[whispers] They've issued
an arrest warrant for Chief Cheon.
[door opens, closes]
What is it?
The JIH has a warrant.
They'll be coming for you soon, sir.
[inhales deeply]
So they're finally doing it.
They're making a move.
Better get going.
Forget it.
It won't solve anything if I run.
I need you to take out Hwang
for good, Kitae.
That's the only way I survive.
Tell me you understand.
Yes, absolutely.
[engine idling]
Go to your hotel, take a hot shower,
and get some good rest.
My investigators will ensure
you get to the airport safely tomorrow.
Let's hope the two of us
never meet in Korea again.
Chief Cheon Seokjung.
I'm Jang Geonyoung.
Nice to finally meet you.
I've always wanted to introduce myself.
It's a big honor to have you visit.
So, shall we?
[Jaeho] Right this way.
Get moving, okay?
Choi Yuji.
You did well.
[Jaeho] Listen, I want you to handle
the interrogation of Chief Cheon yourself.
This is a direct order from Advisor Jang,
so don't disappoint us.
[both slurping]
[exhales]
Are you sure
that we should use Colonel Baek for this?
-I'm on the fence.
-Uh-huh.
Baek's up to it.
I wanna see what his strategy is.
This book documents
a 70 billion won slush fund,
which you moved to Japan.
Choi Yuji, the head of the Ikeda clan,
already testified.
She managed the fund.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What are your ties to the Ikeda family?
How about this.
Where did you get the money?
[on speakers] Chief Cheon.
If you continue to remain silent,
we'll have no choice
but to consider it an admission of guilt.
[sighs]
Do you…
really want me to be honest here?
Just remember…
your brother's not gonna look good.
Bit of a minefield, eh?
[chuckles]
You can pretend, but I know you're lying.
[microphone feedback]
[Geonyoung] Ah, ah.
They can hear me, right?
-[Jaeho] Yeah.
-[Geonyoung clears throat]
Well, Colonel.
I think that's enough for today.
You must be getting tired.
[chuckling]
[electricity buzzes]
[door locks]
[sighing] You gotta be kidding me.
A literal shithole.
[phone ringing]
[sighs]
[Kitae] How's Cheon doing?
He's been keeping his mouth shut,
but he won't be able to hold out.
Once he starts talking, it's all over.
You know that, right?
No, I'm putting an end to it.
He needs to hold out a little longer.
What's your angle now?
You just keep a close eye on him, okay?
Oh, and, where's Choi Yuji?
She was released. She's at a hotel.
She's going back to Japan
on the first flight tomorrow.
Which hotel?
You won't be able to get to her.
The place is crawling with armed guards.
[shouting] I said, which hotel?
[sighs]
Tower Hotel, Room 925.
[phone slams into cradle]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Colonel Baek…
You heading home yet?
I have a few more things to do, sir.
Don't push yourself too hard.
See you tomorrow.
[♪ music continues]
-[door closes]
-[sighs]
Director Baek,
you're not allowed to see her.
[groans]
[grunting, groaning]
[hammer cocks]
[door closes]
[exhales deeply]
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
It was my only option.
I would've done the same thing.
Don't apologize, please.
What are you going to do now?
I told you already.
I have to see it through.
I've come this far.
We could go to Japan together,
couldn't we?
We could…
just start over.
You know my hands are tied right now.
Kitae.
You might die here.
Go wait for me in Japan.
As soon as I take care of this,
we'll start over, okay?
I'm pretty sure that's a goodbye,
isn't it?
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[breathes deeply]
What we had was nice, wasn't it?
It was pretty good.
[Kitae] It was nice.
We'll be able to… meet again, right?
[Kitae] Yes, we will.
I'll see you in Ikaino
for a big bowl of rice soup.
Just like old times.
I need you to promise me…
that you'll stay alive.
I will, I promise.
I'll get to Japan.
Please, Kitae…
when that day comes, let's do it right.
Let's not screw up again.
Love is too special.
We won't mess it up.
I promise, Yuji.
ARMY HEADQUARTERS
I'd like to thank all the commanders
for attending this meeting today.
Above all,
I expect you all to make national security
your number one priority.
CHIEF OF STAFF, R.O.K ARMY
Please commit yourself
to the rule of law and order,
and work tirelessly
to regain economic stability.
[laughing]
Oh, shoot, sorry about that.
Sorry I'm late. Apologies.
Oh, sorry, General.
Uh, keep talking. [chuckles]
-[exhales loudly]
-Some water, sir?
[Mujin scoffs]
-Very well. If there are no objections…
-[exhales loudly]
…I'd like to ask the head
of the JIH a brief question.
You know, before we proceed further.
Yes, General Jang?
I hear you've been extremely busy.
[chuckles]
Extremely? No, sir. No, I'm just…
I'm just trying to do good work
at the job I've been given.
[chuckles] Is that right?
-Yes.
-Then answer me this.
Did I ever give an order
for you to take over as chair
of the vice ministers' council?
Uh, with martial law in effect,
there seemed to be a lot of confusion
with the jurisdictions
of different ministries,
so I thought it'd be good for the JIH to--
And how do you explain taking Chief Cheon
into punitive custody without permission?
Let me guess, you were
going to report that to us after?
Uh, no, sir, no.
You'll recall my reports
on credible suspicions
of illicit slush fund transactions--
[shouting] Who the damn hell are you?
Hwang Daesik, nice to meet you.
-[officer 1] Sir, Hwang is a good man.
-Do you…
He wouldn't go
behind your back deliberately.
Please be lenient with him.
[officer 2] I agree, sir. General Hwang
has a lot on his plate right now.
I'm sure this was
just a well-meaning blunder.
Is this the duty of an honest soldier?
No, a good soldier knows their role
and they stick to it with integrity!
If you want to sneak around
and play politics with each other,
then please do me a favor
and get out of my sight right now!
General Jang.
My sense of loyalty got the better of me.
I'll try to be careful of that.
"Loyalty"?
That said,
we still intend to carry out
a full investigation
into all who have amassed illicit wealth.
ILLEGAL SLUSH FUND EXPOSED
SIGNS POINT TO KCIA INVOLVEMENT
"Chief of Staff Cheon Seokjung's
Illegal Slush Fund Scheme Exposed.
All Signs Point Directly Toward…
KCIA involvement."
DEPUTY DIRECTOR PYO HAKSU
Yeah, pretty punchy headline.
Director Baek!
[anchor] The Joint Investigation
Headquarters announced this morning…
-Hey. What's going on?
-…ledger documenting illegal slush funds
allegedly maintained by
the Chief of Staff, Cheon Seokjung.
The news is sending shock waves
throughout the country…
Did you know about this?
…records of tens of billions of won
in illicit funds, prompting…
Oh, fuck, we're screwed! Goddamn…
…the KCIA. According to reports,
-the ledger contains…
-[phone ringing]
…detailed records spanning several years,
documenting how the funds
were accumulated and distributed.
Chief of Staff Cheon Seokjung
is currently being held for questioning
at the Joint Investigation Headquarters,
as government officials
continue to examine
how the slush fund was created
and where the money was spent.
The Joint Investigation Headquarters
stated that it will make further…
[Kitae] Yes?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
That bastard Hwang.
He never reported it to us.
What he's doing is completely outrageous.
[Mujin] That son of a bitch must really
think I'll just roll over 'cause of this.
Madam Shin,
what's the best course of action?
What should I do about that asshole?
Well, he must be very pleased
with himself right now.
Sometimes it's good to let a man
enjoy his little victories while he can.
Show some restraint.
Wouldn't you agree, Director Baek?
General, don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
A crisis is an opportunity.
You'll take care of what, exactly?
General Jang.
Be patient. He knows what he's doing.
Baek, be honest.
Is it true? Seventy billion?
[scoffs] No, it's absurd.
It's all lies that Hwang cooked up.
[Mujin groans]
[chuckles] You're right.
Cheon isn't the kind of man
who'd do something like that.
If there's one thing I know about him,
he'd never mess around with money.
Seokjung and I graduated together.
He was ranked first.
And I was ranked second.
[chuckles]
In any case, I'm happy
to entrust this to you, Director.
Yes, sir, I'm on it.
I'll be in touch before long.
Heaven Cloud Pavilion. Do you know it?
Well, it's where Bae Geumji worked.
One of those old courtesan houses.
Hwang Daesik is going to be there
to have some drinks.
[♪ tense music playing]
Weren't you planning
to get this over with and kill him?
You know about that?
You're probably desperate, aren't you?
You're out of options now.
When will he be there?
You broke a girl's heart.
I saw you in my dream last night,
Director Baek.
I remember you were out swimming
in deep blue sea water.
You kept calling out to me,
saying I should join you.
[giggling]
Then earlier today, before my prayer,
I did a cleansing ritual and…
what a surprise…
I saw your face again.
I could see it so clearly.
And guess what?
I could tell you'd broken up with someone.
Your expression was clear.
But there are plenty of women out there.
So bury the memories in your heart,
and abandon past regrets.
It's all right, Kitae.
Somebody new is waiting.
Hmm?
[giggles]
Oh, I'll keep you posted on Hwang Daesik.
HEAVEN CLOUD PAVILION
[Kihun] It's at Heaven Cloud Pavilion.
I confirmed the reservation
under Colonel Ahn's name, sir.
It's for the 13th?
That's right.
Get some men you trust,
make sure they're ready.
Pyo should be left out of this.
Yes, sir. I'm on it.
[knocks on door]
[door opens]
[sighs loudly]
I did my research.
That guy Jang Geonyoung?
I tried digging deep,
and it brought up absolutely nothing.
Nobody's close to the guy.
He's like a deserted island. All alone.
[chuckles]
Uh, so…
Sorry about that.
Anyway, the bottom line is…
[exhales sharply] …there is someone
that might be close enough to him.
Oh Yejin, the female prosecutor.
Not his younger sister?
Well, she still lives alone,
no close friends,
no guitar anymore.
She works at the factory still,
but no matter how I look,
there's nothing we can pin on her.
One thing's clear about Jang, though.
He's spent nine years
waiting for an opportunity.
Just to bring you down.
[Kitae scoffs]
[chuckles]
You can go.
Sir, I apologize.
Pyo Haksu. You find anything yet?
Nothing that suggests he's been in contact
with the JIH up to this point.
I'll continue to monitor him.
What made you want to see me again?
The two of us
don't exactly have a cordial,
coffee-house kind of relationship.
[♪ gentle music playing on speakers]
I suppose you shouldn't have come, then.
What?
Wow, that's bitter.
I'm sure you came
because you got worried, right?
Cheon Seokjung's picture
is on the front page,
accusations are flying,
and your brother won't tell you anything.
You're completely in the dark.
I know you're anxious.
Hey.
Just spit out what you came to say.
All right.
Park Changbae.
Where is he?
We've been looking everywhere
and still have no clue.
We don't know if he's dead or alive.
You haven't been able
to reach him either, have you?
[sighs]
My bet is your brother made him
so terrified, he fled the country.
Then again,
Kang Daeil wound up dead,
he wouldn't want the same fate.
You little shit!
Watch your damn mouth, you bitch.
Did you forget what happens
when you challenge my brother?
Oh, of course not.
I'm well aware
of what Director Baek Kitae can do.
And I know exactly
who killed Kang Daeil, too.
That's right. It wasn't suicide.
It was him.
Your own brother took him out. You get it?
[gasps]
[Yejin] Oh, man.
[breathing shakily]
Hi, Minju. It's Uncle Kihyun.
Is your mom around?
Where did she go?
-[typewriter keys clacking]
-[phone ringing]
Please make sure
that your mother calls me, all right?
Mm-hmm. Mmm.
-I won't be gone long.
-Yes, sir.
Anything happen while I was gone?
Uh, Miss Oh.
Mr. Jang. He wants to speak with you.
[Yejin sighs]
[knocks on door]
Yeah?
You wanted me, sir?
Well, you've been gone a lot.
Come take a seat.
These are records of Ikeda Yuji
laundering Cheon's slush funds in Japan.
Take a look.
[grunts]
So where were you today anyway?
Baek Soyeong met me for coffee.
Okay, why did you meet with her, then?
Because of a dealer named Park Changbae
who works for her.
He was pushing meth in Busan,
but he suddenly vanished, so…
I met with her briefly. Big deal.
I told you to hold off for now.
[sighs]
I'm not gonna do that, sir.
Want me to just send you back
to Busan, Yejin?
The reason I'm here
is to bust drug dealers.
I honestly don't give a damn
about the slush fund.
A drug dealer should go down for drugs.
And that includes Baek Kitae.
He belongs in prison,
and until I catch the guy,
I'm not going back, all right?
The money he brought in
from his meth empire
is in the slush fund!
Then answer me. Why?
Why drop the drug charges?
[♪ tense music playing]
What about this don't you get?
[Yejin scoffs]
You listen to me.
You've really been confusing
the shit out of me lately.
Are you actually trying to
bring down a drug lord,
or are you just backing military trash
so you can take power later on?
So tell me…
what exactly is your real objective here?
[Minju crying faintly]
Minju. Minju? Hey, Minju.
Are you all right?
-Uncle Kihyun.
-Mm-hmm?
-[sobbing]
-Ah, shit.
[hurried footsteps]
[gasps] Soyeong. Soyeong. Hey.
[Soyeong breathing shakily]
Soyeong. Hey, what's wrong? Huh?
What is it?
[screaming]
[Kihyun] Hey!
[continues screaming]
[glass shatters]
-Get away!
-Soyeong! Soyeong!
-[continues screaming]
-[object smashes]
[Soyeong] Get away from me!
[screaming] No, no! Get away!
It's me! Soyeong!
Hey! It's me, Kihyun. It's Kihyun.
Yeah. [breathing heavily]
[object thuds]
It's me. It's me.
-[breathing heavily]
-[Soyeong breathing shakily]
Da… Daeil.
[sobbing]
I'm sorry.
[♪ somber music playing]
[sobbing] I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-[breathing heavily]
[sobbing]
I'm sorry.
You're all right, hey.
It's okay.
-It's okay.
-I'm so sorry.
[crying, sobbing]
-Minju…
-Hey, Minju's all right. Minju's fine.
-Minju.
-She's fine, okay?
Minju.
-Minju. Dad's here! Don't be scared!
-[grunting]
-Minju, Dad's here!
-[grunting] Hey, no…
-No, stop, Soyeong.
-Hey, Minju!
-Minju! [screams]
-That's enough.
-Soyeong, no!
-Minju!
Minju! [gasping, screaming]
HANGUK UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
[Kitae breathing heavily]
[exhales deeply]
Did you know Soyeong was like this?
That it was this bad?
If I had, I wouldn't have left her alone.
She'll be fine once she gets treatment.
I'm going to do
everything I can to help her.
Are you capable of regret?
What?
Do you ever regret…
the way you've lived your life?
[scoffs]
What the hell did you just say?
Who do you think put food on your table
all these years?
I was the one earning the money
that fed and clothed you.
I put you through the Military Academy.
You've kept your mouth shut all this time,
and suddenly you've got
a pang of conscience?
And did you notice?
You didn't even realize
what was going on with your own sister!
Just carry on and forget it!
While I take care of everything!
Don't say that!
You have got to stop pretending
to be responsible for everything.
Soyeong and I always listened to you.
We spent our whole lives
doing your bidding.
If I had known you were gonna
end up like this,
I would never have lived that way.
Sure, you built a drug ring just for us.
Not cause of your bottomless,
all-consuming ambition.
[grunting]
How dare you, you little shit.
[both breathing heavily]
[Kitae exhales sharply]
This is exactly what you did back then.
You never asked about the gun I stole…
or why I shot him in the first place.
Whether it was right or wrong.
You never once said
a single word about it.
Everything went bad from then on.
[♪ somber music playing]
If you were really that unhappy
about me saving your life,
you could've said so.
From now on, live how you want.
Chief Cheon, I hope you slept a little.
It's not a five-course dinner,
but I thought I'd bring you
something to eat.
Here.
You should have a little soju too.
[Seokjung groans softly]
[Geonyoung sighs]
[scoffs]
[exhales]
CHIEF OF STAFF TO THE PRESIDENT
CHEON'S SLUSH FUND SCANDAL
So, that money.
What were you planning to do with it?
And it was all from drugs, right?
All 70 billion?
Looks like you were planning to use it
to make yourself president.
Wait a second.
If you'd been able to pull that off,
meth would've become
our biggest national industry.
[laughing]
It was Baek Kitae's idea though, right?
Man, you're really desperate
to catch Baek Kitae, aren't you?
You must still be holding a grudge…
over what he did to you. [chuckles]
Come on, you and Kitae?
When it really comes down to it,
you guys are two of a kind,
yeah?
[chuckles]
[exhales loudly]
Hmm.
Seems like talking's unproductive.
[laughs]
-What, am I gonna be tortured next?
-Torture?
That's always been your specialty.
Ya know, waterboarding and all that?
Killed plenty of guys like that
back in the day, didn't you?
All the techniques you used
back then are still around.
Your methods are being carried on
by the next generation.
We're ready.
[♪ tense music playing]
Clothes off.
[grunting]
[water bubbling]
[gasping]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
I think the madam here
knows Hwang Daesik pretty well by now.
Whenever he plans to meet someone
discreetly, this is where he brings them.
HEAVEN CLOUD PAVILION
From what I've gathered,
he goes there regularly,
at least once a month.
He usually arrives in the evening
and stays for around three hours.
This house is about a hundred meters
from Heaven Cloud Pavilion,
so we'll be using it
as our base of operations.
The owner and his family
have already been sent out of town.
This is C-4.
They used it for breaching
and demolition during the Vietnam War.
It has a lethal radius of 50 meters,
and about the same explosive power
as six hand grenades.
As you can see, it's fitted with a timer.
Once we activate the detonator
remotely from the operations base,
-it'll start counting down.
-[ticking]
[Kihun] Now, if you cut this red wire,
the countdown will stop.
It has to be the red wire.
If you cut the blue one by mistake,
it'll go off immediately.
All the pieces are in place.
Director.
Shall we do this?
[lighter flicks open]
Start it.
[ticking]
Uh, I know that everyone's been busy
serving the country,
so I appreciate you making the time.
In return, I can promise you one thing…
'cause you're my friends,
you're gonna be treated right today!
[all laughing]
All right, with that in mind…
[groans]
Raise a glass.
-We are…
-[all] We are one!
[exhales loudly] Huh?
I didn't gather you all here
just for fun today.
I also wanted to introduce you
to the newest JIH member.
This man is, well, how should I put this…
He's the brains
behind our latest operation. [chuckles]
Our very own Zhuge Liang.
Let's welcome our advisor, Jang Geonyoung.
Nice to meet everybody.
Given the rise of instability and crime,
I plan to do my absolute best
for the Joint Investigation Headquarters,
rooting out corruption,
abuses of government power,
and money laundering
taking place overseas.
I appreciate your support.
Let's hear it for him.
[ticking]
Wait a minute, isn't that…
Director.
Isn't that your brother?
What did you say?
[breath trembles]
Sir!
I got into a minor accident on my way.
Sorry I'm late.
Oh, no. You're not hurt, are you?
No, sir. I'm fine.
I see you've got good looks
and spirit, too.
Tell me your name?
Lieutenant Colonel Baek Kihyun, sir!
All right. Happy to have you here.
Much appreciated.
Colonel Baek, take a seat down there.
Yes, of course.
Thank you.
[ticking]
[breath trembling]
This time, how about
we let Colonel Baek take the lead.
Just give us a nice, proud "We are."
We are!
[all] We are one!
[officer grunts, laughs]
-[Hwang] What's this?
-Hey, not yet. What's going on?
I don't believe I called for you.
Well, General,
I couldn't help myself. [giggles]
I called for them, sir.
[ticking]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]